Finding Aid to the San Francisco Department of Public Health AIDS Office records SFH 4
San Francisco History Center, San Francisco Public Library
- Contracts and Related Documents, 1984-1993; Record Group 2; 39 Cubic Feet
  - Departmental Correspondence, Memos, Reports and Subject Files, 1989-1992; Series 19
    - Long-range Planning Documents of AIDS Office (Towards 1989/90 Five Year Plan), 1 Cubic Feet
      - San Francisco's Response to AIDS: Status Update 10/85 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Articles and Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - 1987 Survey of Service Providers/Agencies for Planning Purposes (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Evaluation of California's AIDS Community Education Program 8/87 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Articles and Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - 1989 Survey of Service Providers!Agencies for Planning Purposes (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - AIDS Office Annual Report, 1987/88 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - AIDS Office Annual Report, 1988/89 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Community-Based Planning, 1989/90 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Forensic AIDS Project Information (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Problem of Dementia (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Minutes, Reports, and Other Documents Towards Five Year Plan (l/89-12/89) (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Group Four: Support Services (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Planning Documents, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Planning Documents, Undated (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Pieces and Drafts of 1989/90 Five Year Plan (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Publications on Planning Process (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Developing Long Range AIDS Plans in New York City and San Francisco Udall, Linda et al., 1989 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - AO Staff Output, Prevention, Surveys and Memos
      - Articles, Papers, and Presentations by AO staff (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - Substance Abuse and Prevention. Other Information (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - Substance Abuse and Prevention. Other Information (Box 65, Folder 21)
      - Prevention Articles (Box 65, Folder 22)
      - American Indian AIDS Prevention. Survey proposal (Box 65, Folder 23)
      - KABB Surveys, various (Box 65, Folder 24)
      - RFP Coordinator's Office: Memos & General Information, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Reports, Surveys, and Other Monographs, 1 Cubic Feet
      - Monographs Published by the SF Department of Public Health
        - Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome: Screening Protocol and Resource and Referral Lists SF Dept of Public Health, May 1983 (Box 66, Folder 1)
        - AIDS/Gay Male Sexuality Counselling Tom Smith, MD; Alcoholism Evaluation and Treatment Center, SFDPH 1983 (Box 66, Folder 2)
        - Comprehensive Plan to Reduce Spread of HIV among IVDUs. Community Substance Abuse Services AIDS Office, SFDPA 1992 (Box 66, Folder 3)
        - Guide to Servicesfor Women at Riskfor HIV/AIDS in San Francisco Perinatal AIDS Prevention Proj, Bureau Family Health SFDPH 1989 (Box 66, Folder 4)
        - Help With HIVInfection; A Resource Guide; SF Dept ofPublic Health. 1988, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 5)
        - HIV & Adolescence: Facing the Challenge of the 90's Community Public Health Services SFDPH, Special Programs for Youth, Adolescent HIV Coalition 1991 (Box 66, Folder 6)
        - HIV & Adolescence: Issues in San Francisco -1992 Community Public Health Services SFDPH, Special Programs for Youth, Adolescent HIV Coalition 1992 (Box 66, Folder 7)
        - Joint Task Force on HIV Epidemic; Second Decade Response to HIV/AIDS in SF; SFDPH 1994 (Box 66, Folder 8)
        - People of Color and HIV/AIDS: Asian/Pacific AIDS Coalition, American Indian AIDS Institute, Black Coalition on AIDS, Latino Coalition on AIDS/SIDA, and AIDS Office SFDPH [1992] (Box 66, Folder 9)
        - Proceedings of AIDS Symposium Held at San Francisco Civic Auditorium; May 22, 1983 by DPH (Box 66, Folder 10)
        - Reportfrom the Committee for Non-Acute Servicesfor Persons with AIDS (aka the "Blum Report") Henrik L. Blum, MD, MPH Chair. San Francisco Department of Public Health 1989 (Box 66, Folder 11)
        - Voices of Experience: A Study of Client Experience with HIV Services in San Francisco Mayor's HIV Health Services Planning Council and AIDS Office SFDPH. 1994 (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Surveys: KABBs (Knowledge, Attitudes, Beliefs and Behaviors) and Others
        - Report on a Baseline Survey of AIDS Risk Behaviors and Attitudes in San Francisco's Latino Communities AIDS Office, SFDPH 1987 (Box 66, Folder 13)
        - Baseline Survey of AIDS Risk Behaviors and Attitudes in San Francisco's Black Communities Polaris - for AIDS Office, SFDPH. 1988-1989 Two Volumes (Unbound) (Box 66, Folder 14-15)
        - AIDS in the Asian Community: Focus Group Report on Needs Assessment Methodologies; Asian AIDS Project 1987 (Box 66, Folder 16)
        - Report on an AIDS KAAB in SF's Japanese Communities Asian AIDS Project, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 17)
        - Report on an AIDS KAAB in SF's Chinese Communities Asian AIDS Project, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 18)
        - AIDS Knowledge, Attitudes, Beliefs, and Behaviors in a Household Survey of Filipinos in San Francisco Filipino Task Force on AIDS and AIDS Office, SFDPH 1990 (Box 66, Folder 19)
        - AIDS KAAB in SF's American Indian, Filipino, & Latino Gay & Bisexual Male Communities, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 20)
        - Young Men's Survey; Principle Findings and Results. Presented to SF Health Commission, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 21)
      - Monographs from Other City Agencies
        - AIDS/ARC Discrimination Public Hearing SF Human Rights Commission, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 22)
        - An Agenda for Action; Frank Jordan's HIV/AIDS Plan 1991 (Box 66, Folder 23)
        - Guide to City Hall; A Resource Book for the Lesbian and Gay Community Lesbian and Gay Mayoral Appointees Caucus, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 24)
        - HIV/AIDS Housing Needs Assessment SF Redevelopment Agency, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 25)
        - Lesbian/Gay Health Services Annual Report 1991 (Box 66, Folder 26)
        - Mayor's Call to Action on the HIVEpidemic; Draft Report ofthe Mayor's HIV Task Force Addressing Critical Gaps in HIV Care and Prevention Services Art Agnos, Mayor 1990 (Box 66, Folder 27)
        - Teacher's Curriculum Guide on AIDS for Middle School and High School Teachers SFDPH and SF Unified School District 1987 (Box 66, Folder 28)
        - Women and HIV (two day conference; May 7-8, 1992) Sponsored by SF STD Prevention Training Center (Box 66, Folder 29)